Let's jump on to the command and control section.
So here we are using X3 RDP to take remote connection from the device.
So the modified set of registries and firewalls in the previous the lateral movement section
and in the command and control section we are going to use RDP for our C2C.
We can take a higher level screen shots like we can get a clear picture to control the device.
So let's move on to the Kali device and we'll give X3 RDP.
We need to give the user name here.
The user name was we know who will be the target and which user we have added.
So the password was a password and the IP was on 9th root.168.18.94.
So once I execute this RDP giving a small console and it was giving and it was showing
the current image, right, even I can control the disk it out from here.
I can open the command room and I can type or anything from here.
I can open the file explorer even I can use browser everything, right, so I can download
something from Chrome and I can do anything instead of machine.
I can create a new user, right.
So this is one of our full mechanism in coming up with the lateral movement and the command
and control.
If we if the protect is get an actual image of the RDP so the clear picture of an RDP so
they can use anything inside a machine as like a legitimate user.
The host will not the host will not know what happening in the back and see the host
how it's looking like it's it do not know what what's going on inside the machine but
in the back and so we can do anything it can we can do anything inside the machine, right.
So this is one of the protectors turn coming up coming up to hijacking or doing something
inside malicious activities inside the machine.
So they can you they can do anything they can zip any file they can upload any file they
can they can download anything or anything or anything, right.
We are controlling the machine in an interactive way rather than the command form, right.
So this is called a send command and control many of them have a question why in the execution
part will be get a C2C in my turn way there is they have added a command and control
separately the command actual command and control will be like this we will be getting get
a clear picture about the target and we can do anything inside the machine.
So controlling the device in the command room will be little bit difficult you needs to execute
multiple commands to do something but if you have a if you have this GUI interface you
can do anything inside of the device so we will hop off from here and we will connect
and continue our discussion on the next video see you guys online.